Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Arts and Media Serials TAM.772
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Arts and Media Serials
1893-2013
1960-1989
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
TAM.772
10 Linear Feet in 18 manuscript boxes and 9 flat boxes
The Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Arts and Media Serials contains over 200 titles on arts and media in the United States, Europe, and other countries in the 19th and 20th centuries. The collection dates between 1893 and 2013, with the bulk of the material dating from the 1960s through the 1980s. Topics include literature, broadcast media, journalism, theater, and literature and communication studies in colleges and universities.
Arrangement
Serials in this collection are arranged alphabetically by title.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to users without restriction.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection combines serials relating to arts and media drawn from two discrete groups of material held by the Tamiment Library. The first was a partially inventoried backlog of serials, received by the library through donations, subscriptions, and in archival collections. The second group consisted of around 1,700 serials, newspapers, and magazines, organized by title as an artificial collection, referred to as Periodicals.001 or Boxed Newspapers. This material was combined, inventoried, and arranged and described in subject-based categories in 2017. The accession number related to this collection is 2017.049.
Scope and Contents
The Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Arts and Media Serials contains over 200 titles on arts and media in the United States (US), Europe, and other countries in the 20th century. The collection dates between 1912 and 2013, with the bulk of the material dating from the 1960s through the 1980s. Topics include the study of American, European, Asian, and African literature and theater, as well as criticism written on these topics, mainly in the US, France, and Canada in the 20th century. Other topics include issues surrounding broadcast media, journalism, communication studies in colleges and universities, community access television, and public radio in New York, California, and other US states in the 20th century. Large runs of titles include The Staff and Zamlungen.
Literature, Modern -- History and criticism.; Literature, Modern -- Study and teaching.; Serials (publications); Journalism -- United States -- 20th century.; Mass media and culture.
- A Mario Rapisardi: Italian Printing Co., Pittsburgh, PA, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Aardvark: Aardvark Publications, Chicago, IL, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Access: National Citizens Committee for Broadcasting, Washington, DC, 1981-1983 (Box 18, Folder 2-3)
- ACRATA: Acrata, San Francisco, CA, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Action Poetique: Action Poetique, Paris, France, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- ACUCAA: Association of College, University and Community Arts Adminstrators, Washington, DC, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- ACUCAA Bulletin: Association of College, University and Community Arts Adminstrators, Madison, WI, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Advice: Center for the Study of Commercialism, Washington, DC, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Afro-Asian Writings: Permanent Bureau of Afro-Asian Writers, Cairo, Egypt, 1967-1973 (Box 1, Folder 8-11, Box 2, Folder 1-4)
- Agency Regulations: Screen Actors Guild, Los Angeles, CA, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Agni: The Agni Review, Inc., Boston, MA, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Ajoblanco: Ajoblanco, Barcelona, Spain, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- ALA Newsletter: African Literature Association, University Park, PA, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Alternative Theatre: Theatre Project, Antioch College, Baltimore, MD, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- American Spectator: The American Spectator, Inc., New York, NY, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
- And Then: The Magic Circle Printing Co., New York, NY, 1989-1993 (Box 3, Folder 4-5)
- Anvil: The Proletarian Fiction Magazine: Jack Conroy and Walter Snow, New York, NY, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Arbeitshefte: Academy of Arts of the German Democratic Republic, Berlin, Germany, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Arena: A Literary Magazine: Fore Publications, Ltd., London, UK, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Arena: A Magazine of Modern Literature: Kenion Press, Ltd., London, UK, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Art Meets Labor: Art Meets Labor, Oak Park, IL, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Art Review: Art Review Inc, Canada, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Arts in Society: Regents of the University of Wisconsin System, Madison, WI, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Artscene: Arts Council at Freeport, Freeport, NY, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Artsnews: Westchester Arts Council, White Plains, NY, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Artweek: Spaulding-Devlin, Inc., San Jose, CA, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Atlas: World Press Company, New York, NY, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Attitude: Dance Giant Steps, Inc., Brooklyn, NY, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- au - arquitectura y urbanismo: Higher Politechnical Institute Jose Antonio Echeverria, Havana, Cuba, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Beatniks from Space: The Neither/Nor Press, Ann Arbor, MI, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Beats the News: Jump Cut, Chicago, IL, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Bertolt Brecht: The Drama Review, New York, NY, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Bertolt Brecht: Theatre Complet: L'Arche Editeur, Paris, France, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Bertolt Brecht Der gute Mensch von Sezuan: Suhrkamp Verlag, Berlin, Germany, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Bertolt Brecht Schriften zum Theater: Suhrkamp Verlag, Berlin, Germany, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Bertolt Brecht: The Days of the Commune: Dunster Drama Review, Cambridge, MA, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Bertolt Brechts Gedichte und Lieder: Suhrkamp Verlag, Berlin, Germany, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Black Ascensions: King Publishing Co., Cleveland, OH, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Black Books Bulletin: The Institute of Positive Education, Chicago, IL, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Black Graphics International on Literature and Art: Black Graphics International, Detroit, MI, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Blues: Lew Ney, New York, NY, 1930 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Bone: The Bone, Seattle, WA, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Boog City: Boog City, New York, NY, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Book League Monthly: Book League of America, Inc., New York, NY, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Book Peddler: National Yiddish Book Center, South Hadley, MA, 1994-1996 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Booktab: Booktab, Inc., New York, NY, 1942-1943 (Box 18, Folder 5-7)
- Brecht Versuche: Suhrkamp Verlag, Berlin, Germany, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 4-5)
- Briv un Redes Fun I.L. Peretz: N. Meisel, New York, NY, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Broadside: Broadside, Ltd., New York, NY, 1984-1987 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Bronx Arts: Bronx Council On The Arts, Bronx, NY, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Bulletin: National Theatre Conference, Cleveland, OH, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Bulletin: The Association of Performing Arts Presenters, Washington, DC, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- By Your Side: Mezhdunarodnaja Kniga, Moscow, Russia, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
- C.W. Bulletin: Contemporary Writers, New York, NY, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Call Sheet: Screen Actors Guild, Hollywood, CA, 1994-1996 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Cine Vue: A Publication of Asian CineVision: Asian CineVision, Inc., New York, NY, 1986-1989 (Box 21, Folder 4-6)
- Community Access TV: Community Access Television, Santa Cruz, CA, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Community Radio Report: Concerned Friends of WBAI, Brooklyn, NY, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Compages: Union of Left Writers, San Francisco, CA, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- CompuMentor: CompuMentor Project, San Francisco, CA, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Concatenator: Western Indexing, Victoria, BC, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Concerned Theater Japan: Concerned Theater Japan Co., Ltd., Tokyo, Japan, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 4-6)
- Contempo: Contempo, Chapel Hill, NC, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Contemporaries: Action/Image Media Group, Union City, NJ, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Coronet: David A. Smart, Chicago, IL, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Creations: Creations Magazine, Roslyn, NY, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Critics Group Series: Critics Group, New York, NY, 1936-1938 (Box 4, Folder 1, Box 6, Box 9, Folder 15, Box 12, Folder 5, Folder 16, Box 13, Folder 9)
- Current Controversy: K.R. Publishing Corp., New York, NY, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Cutting Through: Channel L Working Group, Inc., New York, NY, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Cyrano's Journal: New England Communications Task Force, Inc, Westport, CT, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- D.C. Free Press: D.C. Independent Media Center, Washington, DC, 2001-2002 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Daily Ruckus: Creative Time, Inc., New York, NY, 1975 (Box Shared Tamiment 061, Folder 1)
- Dania Polyglotta: Repertoire Bibliographique Annuel des Ouvrages, Articles, Resumes, etc. en Langues Etrangeres Parus en Danemark: Institut Danois des Echanges Internationaux de Publications Scientifiques et Litteraires, Copenhagen, Denmark, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Das Wort Literarische Monatsschrift: Meshdunarodnaja Kniga Moskau, Moscow, USSR, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- David: The David, New York, NY, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Democratic Communique: Union of Democratic Communications, Oakland, CA, 1986-1993 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Dialectics and Humanism: Polish Scientific Publishers, Warsaw, Poland, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Diego Rivera: Universidad Nacional de Mexico, Mexico City, Mexico, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Directions: Program on Communication and Development Studies, Northwestern University, Evanston, IL, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Dissenting Student: Students Against Social Injustice, Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Dots and Dashes: Morse Telegraph Club, Inc, Chicago, IL, 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 7-8)
- Down Below: Surrealist Research & Development Monograph Series: Radical America / Surrealist Group, Cambridge, MA, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- E.A.T. News: Experiments in Art and Technology, Inc., New York, NY, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Editor & Publisher, The Fourth Estate: Editor & Publisher Co., New York, NY, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- El Caiman Barbudo: El Caiman Barbudo, Havana, Cuba, Undated (Box 18, Folder 16-17)
- ENClitic: enclitic, inc, Los Angeles, CA, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Encore: Encore Press, Inc., New York, NY, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Equity: Actors' Equity Association, New York, NY, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- European Media Business & Finance: EMB&F, New York, NY, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Evergreen: Evergreen Review, Inc., New York, NY, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Exagéré: Archives de l'Avenir: L'Exagere, Paris, France, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Exit Nine: Exit Nine, New Brunswick, NJ, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- FACE: FaGaGaGa, Youngstown, OH, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Federal Theatre News: FTP Locals of the City Projects Council, New York, NY, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Fight to Save WBAI: Friends of WBAI, New Vernon, NJ, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Film & Television Technician (FIT): Association of Cinematograph, Television and Allied Technicians, London, UK, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Film Culture - Expanded Arts: Expanded Arts Center, New York, NY, 1966 (Box Shared Tamiment 061, Folder 2)
- First Stage: First Stage, Lafayette, IN, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Flashes from Hollywood!: Film Technicians of the Motion Picture Industry, Los Angeles, CA, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Flourish: Royal Shakespeare Company Newspaper: Royal Shakespeare Company, Stratford-upon-Avon, UK, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 4-5)
- Foreign Press News: Foreign Press Association, New York, NY, 1955-1961 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Fourth Network: A Study by the Network Project: The Network Project, New York, NY, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- FRA: Elbert Hubbard, East Aurora, NY, 1916 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Freethought History: People's Culture, Kansas City, KS, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Friends of IMA: Institute for Media Analysis, Inc., New York, NY, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Fuse Magazine: Arton's Cultural Affairs Society and Publishing Inc., Toronto, Ontario, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- FYI (For Your Information): The Center for Arts Information, New York, NY, 1986-1992 (Box 8, Folder 7, Box 19, Folder 2-3)
- Global Village: Global Village / National Endowment for the Arts, New York, NY, Undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Harvard Yard Journal: Harvard Yard, Cambridge, MA, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Heirs: Garcia Litho & Printing Service, San Francisco, CA, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Hora de Espana: Revista Mensual: Vinetas de Ramon Gaya, Valencia, Spain, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 11-12)
- Horns of Plenty: Malcolm Cowley and his Generation: Horns of Plenty, Chicago, IL, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Houston Radio Report: KFPT, Houston, TX, 1972, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Humanitarian: Caulon Press / Swan Sonnenschein and Co., New York, NY / London, UK, 1893 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Impact Visuals: Photo & Graphics, Inc., New York, NY, 1989-1992 (Box 8, Folder 15-18)
- In Media's Feces: Strolling Dog Press, New York, NY, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Indian Literature: People's Publishing, Bombay, India, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Ink Reader: Independent Press Association, San Francisco, CA, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Inside Arts: Association of Performing Arts Presenters, Washington, DC, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Inter Actra: ACTRA, Toronto, Ontario, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- International Humanism: International Humanist and Ethical Union, Utrecht, Netherlands, 1966-1973 (Box 9, Folder 6-8)
- IRE Journal: Investigative Reporters & Editors, Inc., Columbia, MO, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Jacobin Books: Jacobin Books, Brooklyn, NY, 1986-1988 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Keynote: The Progressive Music Quarterly: The Workers Music Association, London, UK, 1945-1946 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- KMFB: Austrian Trade Union, Vienna, Austria, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- KRAB News: Jack Straw Memorial Foundation, Seattle, WA, 1984-1987 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- La Banera: Literatura Todo, Barcelona, Spain, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 8-9)
- Lame Monkey Manifesto: Argyle Gargyle, Knoxville, TN, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Language: Circuit Magazine, London, UK, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Leschetizky Association News Bulletin: The Leschetizky Association, New York, NY, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Lie Nailed ... But The Daily News Carries on: Anti-Defamation League of B'Nai B'Rith, New York, NY, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Literary World: Literary World, New York, NY, 1934 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Looking Forward: The Humanists, Los Angeles, CA, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Los Supermachos: Editorial Meridiano, Mexico City, Mexico, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- LTTR no 1: LTTR, New York, NY, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Mac Bird: Grassy Knoll Press, New York, NY, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Maine Commons: Maine Independent Media Center, Waterville, ME, 2002-2005 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Media Culture Review: Institute for Alternative Journalism, Washington, DC, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Menschen: Verlag der Menschen, Leipzig, Germany, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Midwest Alliance: J. Crawford, H. Ehlers, and T. James, Wichita, KS, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Migrant Theater Bulletin: The Drama Review, Berkeley, CA, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Minnesota Review: The Minnesota Review, Milwaukee, WI, 1973-1980 (Box 10, Folder 2-5)
- Modern Drama: The Artcraft Press, Columbia, MO, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Modern Music: A Quarterly Review: League of Composers, New York, NY, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Monogram: Monogram Publications, London, UK, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Monthly Review Press: Monthly Review Foundation, New York, NY, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- More (A Journalism Review): Rosebud Associates, Inc., New York, NY, 1972-1975 (Box 19, Folder 12-14, Box 20, Folder 15-16)
- Music & Life: Music Group of the Communist Party, London, UK, 1961-1963 (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
- Music Front: Pierre Degeyter Music Club of New York, New York, NY, Undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Music is Dangerous: Surrealist Research & Development Monograph Series: Radical America, Cambridge, MA, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- N.Y.S. Museum News: The New York State Museum Associates, New York, NY, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- National Board of Review Magazine: National Board of Review of Motion Pictures, New York, NY, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- National Theatre Conference Quarterly Bulletin: National Theatre Conference, Cleveland, OH, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Network Project Notebooks: The Network Project, New York, NY, 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 5-6)
- Neue Deutsche Blatter: Monatschrift Fur Literatur un Kritik: Neue Deutsche Blatter, Prague, Czechoslovakia, 1934-1935 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- New America: A Review: American Studies at University of New Mexico, Albuquerque, New Mexico, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- New Democracy: National Economy and the Arts, New York, NY, 1933-1934 (Box 19, Folder 16-17)
- New Federal One: Center for Government, Society, and the Arts, Fairfax, VA, 1994-1996 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- New York Actor: Screen Actors Guild New York, New York, NY, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- New York Artist: Cultural Committee of the United American Artists, Local 60, UOPWA, New York, NY, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- New York Hangover: New York Hangover, New York, NY, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- News & Notes: Union for Democratic Communications, Long Beach, CA, 1982-1984 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- News from the Working Theatre: The Working Theatre, New York, NY, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- newsART: Generalist Association, Inc., New York, NY, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Newsletter: The Dramatists Guild, Inc., New York, NY, 1992-1997 (Box 11, Folder 8-9)
- Nightwatch: AKA, Chicago, IL, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 16, Box 19, Folder 15)
- Noetics: Fugitive Press, Syracuse, NY, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- North Coast Times Eagle: R.S. Need and D.H. Lardy, Wheeler, OR, 1987 (Box Shared Tamiment 061, Folder 3)
- Official Bulletin: International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada, Newark, NJ, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Open Dialogue: Association of American Cultures, Washington, DC, 1987-1997 (Box 12, Folder 2, Box 20, Folder 1)
- Optimist: Comic Collective, London, UK, Undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Overload: New People Media Project, Berkeley, CA, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Pacific Northwest Newspaper Guild: Pacific Northwest Newspaper Guild, Seattle, WA, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Pajaro Cascabel: Pajaro Cascabel, Mexico City, Mexico, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Pakn Treger: National Yiddish Book Center, Amherst, MA, 1997-1999 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Palaver: African and Afro-American Research Institute, Austin, TX, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- People's Symphony Concerts: People's Symphony, New York, NY, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Phantasm: Heidelberg Graphics, Chico, CA, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Philadelphia Journalism Review: Philadelphia Journalism Associates, Philadelphia, PA, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Photo Reporter: March of Time, New York, NY, 1937 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Pivot: Pivot, Trinidad and Tobago, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Prairie: Prairie, Milwaukee, WI, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Prairie Fire: Regina Community Media Project, Saskatchewan, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 15-16)
- Prompt: University College London Dramatic Society, London, UK, 1964-1966 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Propaganda Review: Media Alliance, San Francisco, CA, 1987-1991 (Box 12, Folder 14-15)
- Public: Urbana-Champaign Independent Media Center, Urbana-Champaign, IL, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Real People's Music Occasional: Real People's Music, Oak Park, IL, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Red Bass: Red Bass Productions, Inc., New Orleans, LA, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Red Bass: Red Bass Productions, Inc., Tallahassee, FL, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Red Earth: Red Earth, New York, NY, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 6, Box 22, Folder 1)
- Red Letter Days: Political Art Documentation/Distribution (P.A.D.D.), New York, NY, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Redletter: Redbook, Cambridge, MA, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Reel 1: Screen Actors Guild, New York, NY, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Reprints from Sing Out!: Oak Publications, Inc., New York, NY, 1959-1964 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Resources for People's Culture: A Bibliographic Newsletter of Art and Politics: Muriel Hogan, Milwaukee, WI, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Revelations: Fernand Nathan, Paris, France, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Review1 (Monthly Review Supplement): Monthly Review, Inc., New York, NY, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Revolucion y Cultura: Ministerio de Cultura, Havana, Cuba, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Right of Aesthetic Realism to Be Known: Aesthetic Realism Foundation, New York, NY, 1988, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Rolanroc: Alternative Press Syndicate, Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Ronnie Rat Show: Ink Works, Chicago, IL, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Roustabout Reporter: Bindlestaff Family Circus; Autonomadic Bookmobile, New York, NY, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- SCW (Syracuse Cultural Workers): Syracuse Cultural Workers, Syracuse, NY, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Section III: Section III, Seattle, WA, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- ShowBiz West: ShowBiz West, Hollywood, CA, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Sibyl-Child: Sibyl-Child, Baltimore, MD, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Slate: Slate, Berkeley, CA, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Slug & Lettuce: Slug & Lettuce, Richmond, VA, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Soldier: Art Young's First Quarterly, New York, NY, 1922 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Solidarity: New Day Films, Franklin Lakes, NJ, Undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
- South End Press newsletter: Institute for Social and Cultural Change, Boston, MA, 1984-1987 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Soṿeṭish Heymland: Mosḳve, Soveṭsḳi Pisaṭel, Russia, 1969-1972 (Box 25, Folder 1-5)
- Special Issue: Vermont Alternative Media Project (VAMP), Vermont, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Staff: The Staff, Los Angeles, CA, 1971-1973 (Box 22, Folder 4-10, Box 23, Folder 1-8, Box 24, Folder 1-7)
- Strategies: Strategies for Media Literacy, Inc., San Francisco, CA, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Sunspots: SUN Symphony Society, Inc., New York, NY, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Supplement: Association of Performing Arts Presenters, Washington, DC, 1988-1990 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Surrealism: The Octopus Typewriter: Surrealist Movement, Chicago, IL, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Syntheses: Revue Mensuelle Europeenne: Editions Syntheses, Brussels, Belgium, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Tabloid: Tabloid, Stanford, CA, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Techne: Experiments in Arts and Technology, New York, NY, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- This Quarter: Ray Long & Richard R. Smith, Inc., New York, NY, 1930-1932 (Box 13, Folder 20-21, Box 14, Folder 1)
- Thomas Carlyle's Philosophy of Clothes: Haldeman-Julius Company, Girard, Kansas, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Toronto Clarion: Western Gap Communications Co-Operative, Toronto, Ontario, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Travail Theatral: La Cite, Lausanne, Switzerland, 1970-1972 (Box 14, Folder 3-4)
- Tupamaros: NACLA, Berkeley, CA, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Twice a Year: A Semi-Annual Journal of Literature, the Arts, and Civil Liberties: Twice a Year, New York, NY, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Umbra's Blackworks: Society of Umbra, New York, NY, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Unconvention: Independent Media Center of Philadelphia, Philadelphia, PA, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Uptown Beat Literary Quarterly: East Harlem Writing Center, New York, NY, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Voices: Redwood Records Cultural and Educational Fund, Oakland, CA, 1984-1987 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Voices: A Quarterly on Poetry: E. L. Vinal, Brattleboro, VT, 1943 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Washington Book Review: Washington Book Review, Inc., Washington, DC, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Wedge: Wedge, London, UK, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 2)